The Clover Kingdom.
In this place where magic is everything,
there lives one boy who was born without it.
His name is Asta.
His strength and determination helped him become a magic knight.
And despite the many challenges he faces,
he aims for the top and refuses to give up.
Rich or poor, royalty or commoner,
Asta believes anyone can shine.
His mission is to prove that to the whole world,
and to become the next Wizard King.
You know, you and me, we're family, right?
Yeah, of course.
Not by blood or anything, though.
Right.
But we're closer than a lot of people who are related by blood, aren't we?
I guess so. Why, what's up?
I was thinking, you and me, we don't have any real relatives.
But we've got a lot of great friends.
I say, we take all the friends we meet,
and we make them our family instead.
Yeah.
So,
何度も,何度も
目の前の 今を
越えるさ
何度も,何度も
涙を希望に 変えていこう
七色の 日常を進め
永遠に光れ
Fireortunate, shine like a diamond
They start to limit the r ing
minister to thangirls and worry
Don't worry, what isわかりました?
Go see what it's just for generations and progress
I'll stick with your cool hand
The long sticky marks rate
You'll spread the mandal with57
To start overdrive
Wolves writtle
I take it you three are here to give reports to
indeed we just finished a mission in Keaton
ah yes Keaton borders the Diamond Kingdom so the cultural juxtaposition
makes it a popular spot for gourmets you're lucky I wish I could have gone
there instead of patrolling the capital we're not on vacation David all these
missions must be wearing you down I'm fine in times like this it's important
to get enough calories would you like a snack no thanks why are we just making
small talk there's that cocky attitude again he always said he'd become the
Wizard King but after a success in that last battle he became even more arrogant
if only I hadn't been possessed by that elf I could have been useful to Lord
vengeance you know just got lucky that was all the captain's waiting let's go in
sounds good you know I think you need to try being a little bit friendlier what
I'm friendly he doesn't know well sure there's nothing wrong with the way you
are now but it might be nice if you'd consider smiling every now and then or
throw in a joke here and there but I can't even picture what that would be
like so just forget I brought it up sure we'll go one step at a time I suppose
thank you all for your reports Klaus mimosa you know the residents of Keaton have expressed their
thanks to us again you obviously did quite well sir we're honored to hear that captain
now I realize you've only just returned but I have another mission for you
apparently a herd of wild boars came down from the mountains posing a threat to
saucy village I'd ask another squad to take care of it instead but no one's
available I'll do it myself sir a few wild boars would be nothing for me these
aren't normal boars according to the reports we got from saucy village they're
actually magical beasts covered in flames the villagers are terrified I'd like
you all to go there was a squad and eliminate the herd before too much damage
is done Alec Dora will lead this mission yes sir and remember I'm counting on you
right no matter what we're up against I swear I'll outdo you I can't believe the
golden dawn was sent here to rescue us I wish it was the black bulls yeah I want
to see Asta again you know Asta sure do Asta Noel and Magna protected our
village from some really bad guys that's right it was a while ago now but saucy
village is the place where the eye of the midnight Sun was first seen uh-huh the
black bulls defeated some wild boars when they were here too oh yeah then why don't
we make a game out of it let's see if we can take out even more I'm sure the
golden dawn will David we're told the boars are covered in flames that sounds
dangerous they are and they seem to be even more violent than they were last
time we just don't know what we're going to do anymore
oh man you guys feel that it's the kind of mana that only magical beasts have the
villagers can't defeat these Shirin think you can give us a closer look yes of
course stone creation magic stone model of the world let's split up and stop them
before they hurt anyone right wait a second if we don't figure out what made
them so violent in the first place the same thing will just happen again I see
he does bring up a valid point you'd better learn your place you know Lord
Vongens put me in charge of this task so I should make the decisions if defeating
the boars was enough they might as well have sent the black bulls how dare you
easy you know since you're so confident you can go ahead and execute your plan on
your own everyone else ready yourselves for attack sir roger that those
beasts won't know what hit them sorry what is your plan I need to find
something Mimosa time for sand magic suppressing sand math technique
I'll bet with the right seasonings these would make a delightful rose
there now dice magic the gambler's fallacy a one too bad but that's still good
enough to beat a bunch of overgrown pigs wind magic
up ahead there's an area with high magical presence let's take a look
all right I think that fruit is what caused all this interesting so that's why
they're on a rampage then we'll need to eradicate all of it along with the trees
it's growing on good plan you and I can cover that Mimosa you find out what other
areas have trees like this yes sir it was really outspoken earlier if it's to
protect someone he won't hesitate to defy his superiors I doubt he even realizes he
overstepped thank you Knights of the Golden Dawn we are forever in your debt not
only did you stop them but you figured out what was causing them to go berserk and now
that it's fixed we shouldn't need to trouble the magic Knights with this issue again I'm glad we
could put you at ease I bet you're really proud of yourself for proving me wrong what's
with all the flowers oh they're adorable don't you think since the boars have calmed down the
villagers are keeping a few as their pets when you see Asta tell him I've been working on my
spells okay because if he's gonna become the wizard king that I want to be on a magic knight squad so
he and I can work together okay I'll make sure he knows but the next wizard king is actually going
to be me what really excellent job once again everyone now the villagers won't have to live in
fear I wish I could let you relax but we've just received word that a new dungeon has been
discovered and there seem to be suspicious people inside it's located right at the border of Diamond
and Clover it's near Keaton actually apparently people have seen Spade Kingdom soldiers fighting in
that area so whatever's happening Spade is likely involved this is a dire situation but with everything
that's going on here it's unwise for me to leave longress I'd like you to take the lead this time
if possible I wish I could be of service to you captain but at the moment I'm still waiting for
my injuries to heal surely one of the other Knights would be up to the task of course if you think
that'd be best then let's see I'll send Alec Dora sir this is my chance time to prove once and for
all that I'm the one who's the most useful to Lord vengeance are you sure he was the right choice
was he the wrong choice no I just think there was probably a more qualified candidate who could have
been chosen instead I'm listening during the battle against the eye of the midnight sun he managed to
command Magic Knights from all over the kingdom with no time to plan I think he has what it takes to
lead though his impertinence can be irritating what's the matter sir you're different these days and I
mean that in a good way I didn't do anything I just want to make sure this works out yes that's my goal
as well after seeing the way you've changed I want that for him too oh I see we have some bandits on
our hands they're not from spade so this shouldn't be too hard do you want me to get rid of them real
quick you can leave that to me sand binding magic sad box way to go mimosa show us the layout
looks like the treasure room is right here there are two paths that lead to it so we can either come
in from the front or the top then we'll split off into two teams I'm going in via the front entrance
with Shirin Hammond and Lietwal that leaves Klaus mimosa David and you know you guys take the top
understood
magic Knights damn so much for the lookouts
wind magic crescent moon second father he deflected you know spell
have some more
steel creation magic full metal fortress
wow these are some sophisticated techniques for a bunch of bandits
they're using magic items to get a boost smart moon wind creation magic wind blade shower nice try but even that won't be enough to defeat us
we'll cut them off here take this
stone creation magic pursuing crushed rock
what's that do
this dungeon's treasure is ours you got that
don't you know that there's nothing delicious about taking something that isn't yours
glass creation magic
now Lietwal die
willful compass
how dare you use wind magic in front of me
sand magic sand armor guard
no matter how many bandits I have to face
I'm getting all of those magic items back
excellent timing
oh man I tried to get here first so you'd owe me snacks
oh you're already here eh
I guess I shouldn't have expected too much from a group of low-rate bandits
and even with the magic items I lent them
though compared to mine all those trinkets are nothing but trash
that's bold of you to say you're the only trash I see in here
and it's bold of you to insult a former senior magic knight
not that you amateurs would know the difference
I'd watch my tongue
you have no chance of winning
you'd be wise to cooperate
think so
because I have my doubts
sand binding magic
sand armored heavy guard
sand
well that's interesting
it happens to be a perfect match for the spells that I use
black earth creation magic
blood erosion
alexora
plan for covering magic
dream healing flower cradle
guess you're tougher than you look
but we'll see how you do now that I've knocked out one of your men
well this is certainly a predicament
not only does he have the strength to be a magic knight
he's also amplifying his power with a magic item
yes but he's just one man
so we still have the advantage
he has to be aware of that fact
he's confident
what could he be hiding
there's no use in thinking about it too hard right
whatever the enemy throws at us will respond with a delectable counter-attack
glass creation magic
that's cute
steel creation magic
fierce spiral lamps
come on
this can't be what passes for a magic knight squad these days
compass magic
willful compass
there
that one was interesting at least
how's this for interesting
dice magic
the gambler's fallacy
my luck's finally turning around now
unfortunately I can't say the same for you
this is the greatest treasure in the whole dungeon
no matter how powerful a spell you cast
I can use this magic item to suck it right up
are you kidding me
bell
I thought you'd never ask you know
twin magic
swift white bow
did you seriously think that would work
that felt like a gentle breeze from over here
ah that's so annoying
so what's your next move
you guys get the message by now don't you
it's crystal clear
between the necklace and the urn
you've already shown us every trick you've got up your sleeve
and now we can say for certain that you're no match for the golden dawn
I should have helped them fight those wild boars
at least that would have been more fun
if you're trying to provoke me
it's not going to work
stupid brat
I don't know
you look pretty salty over there
it's just as yuno said
our squad will never lose to a weakling
who has to rely on two magic items
if we gave up
it would dishonor the proud name of the golden dawn
let the scrumptious battle begin
if that's what you want
then be my guest
I'll absorb all your mana
luck's on our side
morons
you don't know when to give up
do you
you probably shouldn't be moving around
don't worry marosa i'm fine
help shiren
he needs you more
find us a place with fainter mana
i will try my best to pinpoint some weak spots in the walls
okay
wind magic
tornado fag
you almost had me that time
no it can't be
damn it he's persistent
i'll finish this now
steel magic blazing spiral lance
dice magic
the gambler's fallacy
there
that should be enough to settle it
looks like it's a test of endurance
you'd better hope your mana reserves
don't run out before my magic items break
we're not aiming for you
compass magic
willful compass
a pitfall
that's what they were planning all along
thanks for leaving me with the heavy lifting
don't forget
i still have this
you've reached the end of the line
you fool
i already told you my type of magic
has the advantage over yours
yes and i told you
you can try
but you're simply no match for the nights of the golden dawn
thank you for leading this mission alak dora
you should know sir
at one point i was unable to fight after sustaining an injury
without my squad mates there would have been no hope of success
i see
and what's your view you know
alak dora commanded our team perfectly
why are you trying to make me look good
i'm only telling them the truth
then allow me to be honest as well
when you came to the golden dawn
some of our squad looked down on you for being a commoner
they resented you and were jealous of your powers
and i was no exception
what could possibly possess you to stand up for a group of people like us
we're comrades
i don't need another reason
just that i care
in the past i was also guilty of thinking someone's low social status made them less worthy of respect
but after being rescued by a commoner with no magic or manners i reconsidered my prejudices
don't you dare compare me to him
you know please
apologies
what okay but i'm not sure what you're sorry about
i wouldn't expect you to understand
but i'd be wrong to let it go unsaid
even so i still don't acknowledge you as one of us
are you here to give a report
yes
when we're finished let's all go out to eat together
this is yuno's chance to bond with the squad
that sounds wonderful
hey come back
yuno
you're invited
in fact we specifically invited you
oh i didn't
hammond knows some great restaurants around the royal capital
yeah we thought it might be fun to hit the town with the whole squad and party
you and me we don't have any real relatives but we've got a lot of great friends
let's take all the friends we meet and make them our family instead
are you coming with us yuno
hold on are you blushing of course not
looks like you are
i'm not
oh i want to see
i said no
forever
you is
if you are
you are
in you
wh assembling
Thank you.
叫んでる忘れないように叫んでる
泣きたいほど遠くだって全然届かなくても
信じる君は足掻いて前を向いている
だから枯れないように柄がって描いた夢また歩き出せる
きっと僕を呼ぶ声だ
Schwammedに夢中は真っリーユーヨー!
We're gonna train hard and get even stronger so we can fight the Spade Kingdom!
And defeat the devil! Black Clover page 142 those remaining
Wait... who are you guys? Do you want the devil to die too?
…
Кあ Magnus!